Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Proposals for New LEP Courses, 1980-1982, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - ETS Measures of Global Understanding, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ETS College Students' Knowledge and Beliefs: A Survey of Global Understanding (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Departmental Finances January 1989 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Departmental Finances February 1989 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Departmental Finances March 1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Departmental Finances April 1989 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Departmental Finances May 1989 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Departmental Finances June 1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Departmental Finances July 1989 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Departmental Finances September 1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Departmental Finances October 1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Departmental Finances November 1989 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Departmental Finances December 1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Student Requests 1982-1983- Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Student Requests 1982-1983- Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Student Requests 1983-1984, 1983-1984, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Student Requests 1984-1985- Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Student Requests 1984-1985- Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Student Requests 1985-1986- Folder 1 of 2, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Student Requests 1985-1986- Folder 2 of 2, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Student Requests 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Academic Program Review Budgets, 1987-1989, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Departmental Finances January 1988 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Departmental Finances February 1988 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Departmental Finances March 1988 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Departmental Finances April 1988 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Departmental Finances May 1988 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Departmental Finances June 1988 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Departmental Finances July 1988 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Departmental Finances August 1988 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Departmental Finances September 1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Departmental Finances October 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Departmental Finances November 1988 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Departmental Finances December 1988 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Student Requests 1980, 1980 March-August (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Government Requests 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Government Requests 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Government Requests 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Government Requests 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - FERPA Requests by Government Agencies, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058794 4
  - FERPA Requests by Government Agencies, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SCE Diploma Programs, ca. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - SCE Degree Programs- Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SCE Degree Programs- Folder 2 of 2, 1983-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Middle States Evaluation Report for Diploma Program in Hospitality Management, ca. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Middle States Evaluation Report for Diploma Program in Real Estate, ca. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Middle States Evaluation Report- Paralegal Program, ca. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Report to the Faculty, Administration, Trustees of New York University by An Evaluation Team Representing the Commission of Higher Education of the Middle States Assoc., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Proposal for a Diploma Program in Compensation Management, ca. 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Diploma Program in Personnel Management, ca. 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Diploma Program in Financial Planning, ca. 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Middle States Evaluation Requests- Magazine Diploma Program, ca. 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 July (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 June (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 April (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 March (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 February (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 January (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - A.B.-D.D.S. Program with Faifield University, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Middle States Association Characteristics of Excellence in Higher Education and Handbook for Institutional Self-Study, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Middle States Association LEP Evaluation 2, 1979, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Middle States Association LEP Evaluation 3, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Middle States Association LEP Evaluation 4, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Middle States Association LEP Evaluation Feb. 1984, 1984 February (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Middle States Association Report to the Faculty, Administration, Trustees, Students of NYU, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Middle States Association 1984 Visit, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Report to the State Education Department for MSA, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Off Campus Programs, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Off Campus Programs 2, ca. 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Liberal Education Program Booklets, 1982-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - LEP Workshop on Curriculum Innovations, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence Re: Middle States Assoc. Evaluation Team Visit, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Position Paper on The Undergraduate Core Curriculum, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - SEHNAP Master's Program, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - LEP Publicity and Reports, 1981-1984, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225558 1
  - Report of University Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - FAS Proposal For Revising Undergraduate Liberal Arts Training, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Reports of University Conference on Undergraduate Education, 1977-1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - FAS Approval of Expository Writing Program, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - FAS Resolution on Examination of Undergraduate Degree Requirements, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Interschool Committee: Statement of Aims and Goals for General Education, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Interschool Committee: Integrated Core Curriculum, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Spring 1977 Humanities Seminar Evaluation Project Report, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Humanities Seminar Evaluation Project: Jane Mottus's Junior/Senior Report, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Assessment of the New York University Humanities Seminars (1978-1979) (original) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Dental School Study, 1980-1981, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Seminar Evaluation Project Final Draft 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - A Comparative Analysis of the First Three Semesters of the NYU Humanities Seminars originals, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Dental Selectives, Spring 1979 Evaluation and Report, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Dental Study 9/21/81 Copy, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Assessment of the NYU Humanities Seminars Spring 1977 original, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Assessment of the NYU Humanities Seminars Fall 1977 original, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Middle States Association Evaluation Visit 1973, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Middle States Association 1973 Visit- Folder 1 of 2, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Middle States Association 1973 Visit- Folder 2 of 2, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Periodic Review Report to the Commission on Higher Education of the Middle States Assoc. of Colleges and Schools, 1975-1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Middle States Association 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - MSA Study Abroad Program 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - MSA Study Abroad Program 1981-1982 Completed Form and Correspondence, 1979, 1981-1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - MSA Study Abroad Program 1981-1982 Background Information, 1979-1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - MSA Periodic Review Report, 1974, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Schweitzer Chair 1979-1984- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Schweitzer Chair 1979-1984- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1982, 1987-1988, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
    3 1142 04225557 3
  - Assignment Action by Sports & Recreation Endowment Committee- Folder 1 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Assignment Action by Sports & Recreation Endowment Committee- Folder 2 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SEHNAP Human Relations Program 1984-1985, 1984-1986, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Summer Session Liaison Committee, 1986-1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Summer Session Liaison Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1984 December-1985 January (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1985 February-March (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1985 April-May (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1985 June-July (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1985 June-July (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1985 October-November (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1985 December-1986 January (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1986 February-March (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1986 April-May (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1986 June-July (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1986 August-September (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1986 October-November (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1986 December-1987 January (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1987 February-March (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1987 April-May (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1987 June-July (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1987 August-September (Box 16, Folder 3)
    3 1142 04225569 8
  - Correspondence, 1987 October-November (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1987 December-1988 January (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1988 February-March (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1988 April-May (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1988 June-July (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1988 August-September (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988 October-November (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1988 December (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Community Fund- Folder 1 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Community Fund- Folder 2 of 2, 1987-1988, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Accrediation List, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Registrar Reports 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Registrar Reports 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - The Challenge and the Choice: Investing in Graduate Education and Research in the State University of New York - Report, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - NYS and U.S. Dept. of Ed. Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - NYS and U.S. Dept. of Ed. Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - FERPA Log Book, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Originals of FERPA Guidelines, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - FERPA Hearings-General, 1976, 1981, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Statistics on FERPA Requests by Students & Authorized Agents, circa 1975-1983 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Files for Office of Legal Counsel, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - FERPA 1980 Census, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Typed Transcript from FERPA #1, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    3 1142 04225555 7
  - P.L. 93-380 (FERPA) General and Correspondence- Folder 1 of 2, 1974-1978, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - P.L. 93-380 (FERPA) General and Correspondence- Folder 2 of 2, 1974-1978, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - FERPA Hearing Materials and Transcripts, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1986 January (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1986 September (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1986 October (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1986 December (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 January (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 February (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 March (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 April (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 May (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 June (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 July (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 August (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 September (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 October (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 November (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1987 December (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Departmental Expenditures, 1989 August (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Academic Program Review Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Academic Program Review Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - College of Dentistry Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 1 of 4, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 2 of 4, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 3 of 4, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 4 of 4, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 1 of 4, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 2 of 4, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 3 of 4, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 4 of 4, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 1 of 4, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 2 of 4, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 3 of 4, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - PL 93-380 Record Reviews- Folder 4 of 4, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Keio University Delegation Correspondence, 1987, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - FAS- Applied Sciences Program Correspondence, 1974-1977, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - FAS - Center for Neural Science Correspondence, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - CAS - Terminated and Proposed Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - School of Social Work - Clinical Social Work Program, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - School of Social Work Accreditation 1987, 1982-1983, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - SEHNAP Dept. of Physical Therapy Proposal Supporting Information, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - SEHNAP Dept. of Physical Therapy Proposal, 1984, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - School of Continuing Ed. - Medical Assisting Program, Real Estate Institute, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - SEHNAP - Terminated and Proposed Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - GSAS - Terminated and Proposed Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225554 0
  - GSAS - Developmental Psychology Program, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School of Public Admin. - Student Reactions to College Questionnaire, 1988, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - GSPA - Public Health Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Licensing Requirements and Info for Psychology, 1977-1986, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - SEHNAP Puerto Rico Center, 1978, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - College of Dentistry Review Correspondence, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - College of Dentistry Program Proposals, Reviews, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - College of Dentistry Program Review Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - School of Medicine - Fifth Pathway, Nuclear Medicine Programs, 1971-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - School of Medicine - New and Re-Accredited Programs, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - SEHNAP National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education Visit, 1984, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - SEHNAP Psych 10 Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - GSAS/Cooper Union Engineering Program, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Law School - Chonnam University, Puerto Rico Council, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - WSUC Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Social Work at Dominican College, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - School of Continuing Ed.Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - School of Continuing Ed.Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - School of Continuing Ed.Correspondence, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - School of Continuing Ed.Correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - School of Continuing Ed. Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Correspondence, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Division of Applied Science, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - GSAS, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - GSAS, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - GSAS, 1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - GSAS, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - GSAS/Cooper Union, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - GSAS, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - College of Dentistry- Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - College of Dentistry- Folder 2 of 2, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - College of Dentistry, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    3 1142 04225556 5
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - SEHNAP, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - SEHNAP, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - College of Dentistry, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Business and Public Administration, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Business and Public Administration, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Business and Public Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Business and Public Administration, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square University College, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square University College, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - College of Dentistry, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - College of Dentistry, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Gallatin School, 1986-1987, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Gallatin School, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Gallatin School, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - SEHNAP-University Coordinating Committee, 1977 1978 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Registration Warning Cards, 1977-1978, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - SEHNAP-University Coordinating Committee, 1977-1978, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - School of the Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058793 6
  - School of the Arts, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Tisch School of the Arts, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Tisch School of the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Tisch School of the Arts, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - State Inventory of Programs- Folder 1 of 3, 1977-1980, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - State Inventory of Programs- Folder 2 of 3, 1977-1980, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - State Inventory of Programs- Folder 3 of 3, 1977-1980, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - State Inventory of Programs- Folder 1 of 2, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - State Inventory of Programs- Folder 2 of 2, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Division of Applied Science, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - School of Social Work, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - School of Social Work, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - School of Social Work, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - School of Social Work, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - School of Social Work, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - School of Social Work, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - School of Social Work, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - School of Social Work, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - School of Social Work, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - School of Social Work Accreditation Info.- Folder 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - School of Social Work Accreditation Info.- Folder 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1977-1983 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1977-1983 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - SEHNAP University Coordinating Committee, 1975, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - SEHNAP- Folder 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - General Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225553 2
  - General Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 1 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)